Voices of Civil Rights Project collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series IV: Bus Tour Interviews and Events Moving Images, 2004-2005
  - Subseries I: AARP, 2004, 90 videocassettes (DVCAM), 4 videocassettes (miniDV) and 3 videocassettes (VHS)
    - AFC 2005/015: MV050, 1 DVCAM
      - Unidentified woman interviewed in Oakland, California, 2004-09-05
      - Evelio Grillo interviewed in Oakland, California, 2004-09-05
    - AFC 2005/015: MV051, 1 DVCAM
      - Randolph Allen interviewed by Debra Krol in Oakland, California, 2004-09-05
      - Unidentified woman interviewed in Oakland, California, 2004-09-05
      - William Passero interviewed in Oakland, California, 2004-09-05
      - Katrina Denise Hill-Jones interviewed in Oakland, California, 2004-09-05
      - Pauline Horvath interviewed in Oakland, California, 2004-09-05 (1 of 2)
    - AFC 2005/015: MV052, 1 DVCAM
      - Pauline Horvath interviewed in Oakland, California, 2004-09-05 (2 of 2)
      - Stephen Bingham interviewed in Oakland, California, 2004-09-05
    - AFC 2005/015: MV053, 1 DVCAM
      - Andrew Montgomery interviewed by Sandra Marquez in Oakland, California, 2004-09-06
      - Elizabeth Adams interviewed by Sandra Marquez in Oakland, California, 2004-09-06
      - Jean Jackson interviewed in Oakland, California, 2004-09-06
    - AFC 2005/015: MV054, 1 DVCAM
      - Daisy Williams interviewed by Sandra Marquez in Oakland, California, 2004-09-06
      - Barbara [unidentified last name] interviewed in Oakland, California, 2004-09-06
      - Donna Ray interviewed by Sandra Marquez in Oakland, California, 2004-09-06
    - AFC 2005/015: MV055, 1 DVCAM
      - Robert Mandell interviewed by Sandra Marquez in Oakland, California, 2004-09-06
      - Aggie Rose Chavez interviewed in Oakland, California, 2004-09-06
      - Unidentified man interviewed in Oakland, California, 2004-09-06
      - Frederico Chavez interviewed in Oakland, California, 2004-09-06 (1 of 2)
    - AFC 2005/015: MV056, 1 DVCAM
      - Unidentified interviewed in Oakland, California, 2004-09-06
      - Susie Jemmie Lou David-Clay interviewed by Lydia Lum in Oakland, California, 2004-09-06
      - Ray Magee interviewed in Oakland, California, 2004-09-06 (1 of 2)
    - AFC 2005/015: MV057, 1 DVCAM
      - Ray Magee interviewed in Oakland, California, 2004-09-06 (2 of 2)
      - Laurie Magee interviewed in Oakland, California, 2004-09-06
      - C. Tasmiya King-Miller interviewed in Oakland, California, 2004-09-06 (1 of 3)
    - AFC 2005/015: MV058, 1 DVCAM
      - Unidentified woman interviewed in Modesto, California, 2004-09-08
      - David Dill interviewed in Modesto, California, 2004-09-08
      - Unidentified man interviewed in Modesto, California, 2004-09-08
    - AFC 2005/015: MV059, 1 DVCAM
      - Juanita Jackson interviewed by Debra Krol in Modesto, California, 2004-09-08
      - Hershey Johnson interviewed in Modesto, California, 2004-09-08
      - Lila Frazier interviewed in Modesto, California, 2004-09-08
    - AFC 2005/015: MV060, 1 DVCAM
      - Odessa Johnson interviewed in Modesto, California, 2004-09-08
      - Ruby Jean Kennedy interviewed in Modesto, California, 2004-09-08
    - AFC 2005/015: MV061, 1 DVCAM
      - Unidentified interviews in Oakland, California, 2004-09-06
    - AFC 2005/015: MV062, 1 DVCAM
      - Patricia McCarty interviewed in Modesto, California, 2004-09-08
      - Estella Hernandez interviewed by Sandra Marquez in Modesto, California, 2004-09-08
      - Nita Jones interviewed in Modesto, California, 2004-09-08
      - Zelda Hutcherson interviewed in Modesto, California, 2004-09-08
    - AFC 2005/015: MV063, 1 DVCAM
      - James Sanders interviewed by Sandra Marquez in Los Angeles, California, 2004-09-10
      - Unidentified man interviewed in Los Angeles, California, 2004-09-10
      - John W. Harris interviewed by Debra Krol in Los Angeles, California, 2004-09-10 (1 of 2)
    - AFC 2005/015: MV064, 1 DVCAM
      - John W. Harris interviewed by Debra Krol in Los Angeles, California, 2004-09-10 (2 of 2)
      - Unidentified man interviewed in Los Angeles, California, 2004-09-10
      - Cheryl Brown interviewed by Debra Krol in Los Angeles, California, 2004-09-10
    - AFC 2005/015: MV065, 1 DVCAM
      - Henry Purnell interviewed by Sandra Marquez in Los Angeles, California, 2004-09-10
      - Lucia Su interviewed by Sandra Marquez in Los Angeles, California, 2004-09-10
      - Bruce Cecil interviewed by Sandra Marquez in Los Angeles, California, 2004-09-10
    - AFC 2005/015: MV066, 1 DVCAM
      - Eleanora Yancey interviewed by Sandra Marquez in Los Angeles, California, 2004-09-10
      - Ernest Hamilton interviewed by Sandra Marquez in Los Angeles, California, 2004-09-11
      - Adam Burton interviewed by Sandra Marquez in Los Angeles, California, 2004-09-11
    - AFC 2005/015: MV067, 1 DVCAM
      - Celes King IV interviewed by Lydia Lum in Los Angeles, California, 2004-09-11 (1 of 2)
      - Alexis King Jones Elder interviewed by Lydia Lum in Los Angeles, California, 2004-09-11
      - William Epps interviewed by Lydia Lum in Los Angeles, California, 2004-09-11
      - Henderson Jones interviewed in Los Angeles, California, 2004-09-11
    - AFC 2005/015: MV068, 1 DVCAM
      - Arnett Hartsfield interviewed by Lydia Lum in Los Angeles, California, 2004-09-11
      - Roland Bynum interviewed in Los Angeles, California, 2004-09-11
      - J. L. Ferrell, Jr., interviewed by Sandra Marquez in Los Angeles, California, 2004-09-11
      - John Stock interviewed by Lydia Lum in Los Angeles, California, 2004-09-11
    - AFC 2005/015: MV069, 1 DVCAM
      - Jane Walker interviewed by Sandra Marquez in Los Angeles, California, 2004-09-12
      - Edith Abram interviewed by Sandra Marquez in Los Angeles, California, 2004-09-12
    - AFC 2005/015: MV070, 1 DVCAM
      - Rosentene Bennett Burnell interviewed by Sandra Marquez in Los Angeles, California, 2004-09-12
      - Joe Adams interviewed in Los Angeles, California, 2004-09-12
    - AFC 2005/015: MV071, 1 DVCAM
      - Bernard Parks interviewed by Lydia Lum in Los Angeles, California, 2004-09-12
      - Bobby Bargainen interviewed by Sandra Marquez in Los Angeles, California, 2004-09-12
      - Edward Phillip Powell interviewed in Los Angeles, California, 2004-09-12 (1 of 2)
    - AFC 2005/015: MV072, 1 DVCAM
      - Edward Phillip Powell interviewed in Los Angeles, California, 2004-09-12 (2 of 2)
      - Ethel V. Young interviewed in Los Angeles, California, 2004-09-12
      - Rose Fullialove interviewed in Los Angeles, California, 2004-09-12
      - Barbara Bounds interviewed in Los Angeles, California, 2004-09-12
    - AFC 2005/015: MV073, 1 DVCAM
      - Vasco and Maxine Smith interviewed in Memphis, Tennessee, 2004-09
    - AFC 2005/015: MV074, 1 DVCAM
      - Johnnie Rodgers Turner interviewed in Memphis, Tennessee, 2004-09-18
      - Ernestine McNeil and Geraldine Williams interviewed by Sandra Marquez in Albany, Georgia, 2004-09-19 (1 of 2)
    - AFC 2005/015: MV075, 1 DVCAM
      - Ernestine McNeil and Geraldine Williams interviewed by Sandra Marquez in Albany, Georgia, 2004-09-20 (2 of 2)
      - Maryann Jenkins interviewed in Albany, Georgia, 2004-09-20
      - Etris L. Smith interviewed in Albany, Georgia, 2004-09-20
    - AFC 2005/015: MV076, 1 DVCAM
      - Rutha Mae Harris interviewed in Albany, Georgia, 2004-09-20 (1 of 2)
      - Richard Henry interviewed in Albany, Georgia, 2004-09-20
      - Elza "Pat" Horton interviewed in Albany, Georgia, 2004-09-20
    - AFC 2005/015: MV077, 1 DVCAM
      - Emory Harris interviewed in Georgia, 2004-09
      - Margaret Louise Dudley interviewed in Georgia, 2004-09
      - John "Jack" C. Holz interviewed in Atlanta, Georgia, 2004-09-24 (1 of 2)
    - AFC 2005/015: MV078, 1 DVCAM
      - John "Jack" C. Holz interviewed in Atlanta, Georgia, 2004-09-24 (2 of 2)
      - Tyrone Brooks interviewed by Sandra Marquez in Atlanta, Georgia, 2004-09-24
    - AFC 2005/015: MV079, 1 DVCAM
      - Speeches and choir performance in Atlanta, Georgia, 2004-09-24
      - Virginia Wilder interviewed by Sandra Marquez in Atlanta, Georgia, 2004-09-24
    - AFC 2005/015: MV080, 1 DVCAM
      - Roger Mills interviewed by Sandra Marquez in Atlanta, Georgia, 2004-09-24
    - AFC 2005/015: MV081, 1 DVCAM
      - Virginia "Ginger" Davis Floyd interviewed by Sandra Marquez in Little Rock, Arkansas, 2004-09-26
      - Eliza Jane Ashley interviewed in Little Rock, Arkansas, 2004-09-26 (1 of 2)
    - AFC 2005/015: MV082, 1 DVCAM
      - Margaret Kolb interviewed in Little Rock, Arkansas, 2004-09-26
      - Eliza Jane Ashley interviewed in Little Rock, Arkansas, 2004-09-26 (2 of 2)
    - AFC 2005/015: MV083, 1 DVCAM
      - Robert Graetz interviewed by Sandra Marquez in Columbus, Ohio, 2004-09-28
      - Pamela Hollie interviewed in Columbus, Ohio, 2004-09-28
    - AFC 2005/015: MV084, 1 DVCAM
      - Ruthene J. Pearson interviewed by Sandra Marquez in Columbus, Ohio, 2004-09-28
      - Bessie King Jackson interviewed by Sandra Marquez in Columbus, Ohio, 2004-09-28
      - William Craig interviewed in Columbus, Ohio, 2004-09-28
    - AFC 2005/015: MV085, 1 DVCAM
      - James Brown interviewed in Columbus, Ohio, 2004-09-28
      - Ruth Mathews interviewed in Detroit, Michigan, 2004-09-30
    - AFC 2005/015: MV086, 1 miniDV
      - Dorothy Height interviewed at the National Book Festival in Washington, D.C., 2004-10-09
      - Sharon Holsten interviewed at the National Book Festival in Washington, D.C., 2004-10-09
      - Warren Tsuneishi interviewed at the National Book Festival in Washington, D.C., 2004-10-09
      - Page Precia interviewed at the National Book Festival in Washington, D.C., 2004-10-09
      - Valery Armack interviewed at the National Book Festival in Washington, D.C., 2004-10-09 (1 of 2)
    - AFC 2005/015: MV087, 1 miniDV
      - John Lewis interviewed at the National Book Festival in Washington, D.C., 2004-10-09
      - Bonnie Bundy and Marion Parker interviewed at the National Book Festival in Washington, D.C., 2004-10-09
      - Patricia Rosier interviewed at the National Book Festival in Washington, D.C., 2004-10-09
    - AFC 2005/015: MV088, 1 miniDV
      - Valery Armack interviewed at the National Book Festival in Washington, D.C., 2004-10-09 (2 of 2)
    - AFC 2005/015: MV089, 1 DVCAM
      - Dee Dee Jasmin interviewed by Liz Whitehouse in Las Vegas, Nevada, 2004-10-14
      - Isiah Williams interviewed by Liz Whitehouse in Las Vegas, Nevada, 2004-10-14
    - AFC 2005/015: MV090, 1 DVCAM
      - D. D. Cotton interviewed by Liz Whitehouse in Las Vegas, Nevada, 2004-10-14
      - Tressie Simon interviewed by Liz Whitehouse in Las Vegas, Nevada, 2004-10-14
      - Irvin D. Coker interviewed by Liz Whitehouse in Las Vegas, Nevada, 2004-10-14
      - Barbara U. Geaither interviewed by Liz Whitehouse in Las Vegas, Nevada, 2004-10-14 (1 of 2)
    - AFC 2005/015: MV091, 1 DVCAM
      - Barbara U. Geaither interviewed by Liz Whitehouse in Las Vegas, Nevada, 2004-10-14 (2 of 2)
      - Darell White interviewed by Liz Whitehouse in Las Vegas, Nevada, 2004-10-14
      - Erik Olson interviewed by Liz Whitehouse in Las Vegas, Nevada, 2004-10-14
      - Sharon Hawkins interviewed by Liz Whitehouse in Las Vegas, Nevada, 2004-10-14
    - AFC 2005/015: MV092, 1 DVCAM
      - William Novelli interviewed by Liz Whitehouse in Las Vegas, Nevada, 2004-10-14
      - Alice Key and Jesse D. Scott interviewed by Liz Whitehouse in Las Vegas, Nevada, 2004-10-14
      - Bill Perkins interviewed by Liz Whitehouse in Las Vegas, Nevada, 2004-10-14
    - AFC 2005/015: MV093, 1 DVCAM
      - Ann Pruitt Shough interviewed by Liz Whitehouse in Las Vegas, Nevada, 2004-10-15
      - Unidentified man interviewed in Las Vegas, Nevada, 2004-10-15
      - Unidentified woman interviewed in Las Vegas, Nevada, 2004-10-15
      - John Caragoin interviewed by Liz Whitehouse in Las Vegas, Nevada, 2004-10-15
    - AFC 2005/015: MV094, 1 DVCAM
      - Unidentified woman interviewed in Las Vegas, Nevada, 2004-10-15
      - Unidentified man interviewed in Las Vegas, Nevada, 2004-10-15
      - Unidentified woman interviewed in Las Vegas, Nevada, 2004-10-15
      - Unidentified woman interviewed in Las Vegas, Nevada, 2004-10-15
      - Ronald Russell interviewed by Mamie Moore in Las Vegas, Nevada, 2004-10-15
      - Walt Jordan interviewed in Las Vegas, Nevada, 2004-10-15
      - Dorothy Hamilton interviewed by Liz Whitehouse in Las Vegas, Nevada, 2004-10-15
    - AFC 2005/015: MV095, 1 VHS
      - Nathaniel Lowery interviewed in North Carolina, 2004-08
      - Alice Lowery interviewed in North Carolina, 2004-08
      - Marian Blackwell interviewed in North Carolina, 2004-08
      - Chaney R. Edwards interviewed in North Carolina, 2004-08
      - Joseph Tyler interviewed in North Carolina, 2004-08
      - Charles M. King interviewed in North Carolina, 2004-08
      - Carolyn Edwards interviewed in North Carolina, 2004-08
    - AFC 2005/015: MV096, 1 VHS
      - Mary E. Whittington interviewed in Greensboro, North Carolina, 2004-05-28
      - Carrie Glasper interviewed in Greensboro, North Carolina, 2004-05-28
      - Gertrude Davis interviewed in Greensboro, North Carolina, 2004-05-28
    - AFC 2005/015: MV097, 1 VHS
      - Almetta Monk Revis interviewed in Greensboro, North Carolina, 2004-05-28
      - Genicia E. Brown interviewed in Greensboro, North Carolina, 2004-05-28
      - William Washington and Barbara Washington Brown interviewed in Greensboro, North Carolina, 2004-05-28
      - Joseph Level interviewed in Greensboro, North Carolina, 2004-05-28
      - Ruby Kimble Idlett interviewed in Greensboro, North Carolina, 2004-05-28
  - Subseries II: The History Channel, 2004, 188 videocassettes (miniDV)
    - AFC 2005/015: MV098, 1 miniDV
      - Brian Taylor interviewed by Andy Bowley in Washington, D.C., 2004-08-03
      - Geraldine Phillips interviewed by Andy Bowley in Washington, D.C., 2004-08-03
      - Audrey Straus Koch interviewed by Andy Bowley in Washington, D.C., 2004-08-03
      - Florence Orbach interviewed by Andy Bowley in Washington, D.C., 2004-08-03
      - Mary Y. Betters interviewed by Andy Bowley in Washington, D.C., 2004-08-03 (1 of 2)
    - AFC 2005/015: MV099, 1 miniDV
      - Mary Y. Betters interviewed by Andy Bowley in Washington, D.C., 2004-08-03 (2 of 2)
      - Betty Bunce interviewed by Andy Bowley in Washington, D.C., 2004-08-03
      - Rev. Elbert Ransom, Jr., interviewed by Andy Bowley in Washington, D.C., 2004-08-03 (1 of 2)
    - AFC 2005/015: MV100, 1 miniDV
      - Rev. Elbert Ransom, Jr., interviewed by Andy Bowley in Washington, D.C., 2004-08-03 (2 of 2)
    - AFC 2005/015: MV101, 1 miniDV
      - Rev. J. Samuel Williams, Jr., interviewed by Andy Bowley in Richmond, Virginia, 2004-08-04
      - Doug Wilder interviewed by Andy Bowley in Richmond, Virginia, 2004-08-04
      - Bob Cohen interviewed by Andy Bowley in Richmond, Virginia, 2004-08-04
    - AFC 2005/015: MV102, 1 miniDV
      - Jacqueline Dash Ziglar interviewed by Andy Bowley in Richmond, Virginia, 2004-08-04
      - Willie C. Jones interviewed by Andy Bowley in Richmond, Virginia, 2004-08-04
      - Hugo A. Owens, Sr., interviewed by Andy Bowley in Richmond, Virginia, 2004-08-04 (2 of 3)
    - AFC 2005/015: MV103, 1 miniDV
      - Hugo A. Owens, Sr., interviewed by Andy Bowley in Richmond, Virginia, 2004-08-04 (3 of 3)
      - Paula Owens Parker interviewed by Andy Bowley in Richmond, Virginia, 2004-08-04
    - AFC 2005/015: MV104, 1 miniDV
      - Thad Woodard interviewed by Andy Bowley in Raleigh, North Carolina, 2004-08-05
      - Helen O'Brien interviewed by Andy Bowley in Raleigh, North Carolina, 2004-08-05
      - Raymond Whitsell interviewed by Andy Bowley in Raleigh, North Carolina, 2004-08-05 (2 of 3)
    - AFC 2005/015: MV105, 1 miniDV
      - Raymond Whitsell interviewed by Andy Bowley in Raleigh, North Carolina, 2004-08-05 (3 of 3)
    - AFC 2005/015: MV106, 1 miniDV
      - Garland Knott interviewed by Andy Bowley in Durham, North Carolina, 2004-08-05
      - Fay Mayo interviewed by Andy Bowley in Durham, North Carolina, 2004-08-05
      - Jean Scales interviewed by Andy Bowley in Durham, North Carolina, 2004-08-05
    - AFC 2005/015: MV107, 1 miniDV
      - Linda Beatrice Brown interviewed by Andy Bowley in Greensboro, North Carolina, 2004-08-06
      - Doxie Whitfield interviewed by Andy Bowley in Greensboro, North Carolina, 2004-08-06
    - AFC 2005/015: MV108, 1 miniDV
      - Event speakers and choir in Washington, D.C., 2004-08-03
    - AFC 2005/015: MV109, 1 miniDV
      - Event speakers in Washington, D.C., 2004-08-03
      - Theodore Gaffney interviewed by Hannah Rosenzweig in Washington, D.C., 2004-08-03
      - James Wyckoff interviewed in Washington, D.C., 2004-08-03 (1 of 2)
    - AFC 2005/015: MV110, 1 miniDV
      - Frederick Beckner interviewed in Washington, D.C., 2004-08-03 (2 of 2)
      - James Wyckoff interviewed in Washington, D.C., 2004-08-03 (2 of 2)
    - AFC 2005/015: MV111, 1 miniDV
      - Event speakers and choir in Richmond, Virginia, 2004-08-04
    - AFC 2005/015: MV112, 1 miniDV
      - Event in Richmond, Virginia, 2004-08-04
      - Thelma Robinson interviewed by Hannah Rosenzweig in Richmond, Virginia, 2004-08-04
      - Geraldine Foster interviewed by Hannah Rosenzweig in Richmond, Virginia, 2004-08-04 (1 of 2)
    - AFC 2005/015: MV113, 1 miniDV
      - Ned Cary, Jr., interviewed in Richmond, Virginia, 2004-08-04 (2 of 2)
      - John A. deLoyht interviewed in Richmond, Virginia, 2004-08-04
    - AFC 2005/015: MV114, 1 miniDV
      - Event speakers in Raleigh, North Carolina, 2004-08-05
    - AFC 2005/015: MV115, 1 miniDV
      - Renee King and her mother interviewed in Raleigh, North Carolina, 2004-08-05 (2 of 2)
    - AFC 2005/015: MV116, 1 miniDV
      - Event speakers and performance in Durham, North Carolina, 2004-08-05
    - AFC 2005/015: MV117, 1 miniDV
      - Marjorie Edwards interviewed by Nery Ynclan in Durham, North Carolina, 2004-08-05 (2 of 2)
      - James Pointer interviewed by Nery Ynclan in Durham, North Carolina, 2004-08-05 (2 of 2)
      - Tour of Hayti Heritage Center in Durham, North Carolina, 2004-08-05
    - AFC 2005/015: MV118, 1 miniDV
      - Anthony Layng interviewed by Andy Bowley in Greensboro, North Carolina, 2004-08-06
      - Joyce Johnson interviewed by Andy Bowley in Greensboro, North Carolina, 2004-08-06
      - Nelson Johnson interviewed by Andy Bowley in Greensboro, North Carolina, 2004-08-06
      - Vernon King interviewed by Andy Bowley in Greensboro, North Carolina, 2004-08-06 (1 of 2)
    - AFC 2005/015: MV119, 1 miniDV
      - Vernon King interviewed by Andy Bowley in Greensboro, North Carolina, 2004-08-06 (2 of 2)
    - AFC 2005/015: MV120, 1 miniDV
      - Kay Golden interviewed in Charlotte, North Carolina, 2004-08-07
      - Daisy Stroud interviewed by Andy Bowley in Charlotte, North Carolina, 2004-08-07
    - AFC 2005/015: MV121, 1 miniDV
      - Brumit B. DeLaine interviewed by Andy Bowley in Columbia, South Carolina, 2004-08-08
      - Joseph Jackson interviewed by Andy Bowley in Columbia, South Carolina, 2004-08-08
      - Gretchen Weber interviewed by Andy Bowley in Columbia, South Carolina, 2004-08-08 (1 of 2)
    - AFC 2005/015: MV122, 1 miniDV
      - Gretchen Weber interviewed by Andy Bowley in Columbia, South Carolina, 2004-08-08 (2 of 2)
      - Violet Staley interviewed by Andy Bowley in Columbia, South Carolina, 2004-08-08
    - AFC 2005/015: MV123, 1 miniDV
      - Cleveland Sellers, Sr., interviewed by Andy Bowley in Orangeburg, South Carolina, 2004-08-09
    - AFC 2005/015: MV124, 1 miniDV
      - George R. Dean interviewed by Andy Bowley in Columbia, South Carolina, 2004-08-09 (1 of 2)
    - AFC 2005/015: MV125, 1 miniDV
      - George R. Dean interviewed by Andy Bowley in Columbia, South Carolina, 2004-08-09 (2 of 2)
    - AFC 2005/015: MV126, 1 miniDV
      - Charles Smith interviewed by Andy Bowley in Tallahassee, Florida, 2004-08-12
      - Roddrick Moorer interviewed by Andy Bowley in Tallahassee, Florida, 2004-08-12
      - Patricia Due interviewed by Andy Bowley in Tallahassee, Florida, 2004-08-12 (1 of 2)
    - AFC 2005/015: MV127, 1 miniDV
      - Patricia Due interviewed by Andy Bowley in Tallahassee, Florida, 2004-08-12 (2 of 2)
      - Fred Lee interviewed by Andy Bowley in Tallahassee, Florida, 2004-08-12
      - James Colbert interviewed by Andy Bowley in Tallahassee, Florida, 2004-08-12 (1 of 2)
    - AFC 2005/015: MV128, 1 miniDV
      - Event and performance in Greensboro, North Carolina, 2004-08-06
      - Christine Tarpley interviewed by Hannah Rosenzweig in Greensboro, North Carolina, 2004-08-06
    - AFC 2005/015: MV129, 1 miniDV
      - Ms. Warren interviewed in Greensboro, North Carolina, 2004-08-06
      - Wendell Carr interviewed by Hannah Rosenzweig in Greensboro, North Carolina, 2004-08-06
      - Viola Williams interviewed by Hannah Rosenzweig in Greensboro, North Carolina, 2004-08-06 (1 of 2)
    - AFC 2005/015: MV130, 1 miniDV
      - Joyce Wydell interviewed in Charlotte, North Carolina, 2004-08-07
      - J. C. Jones interviewed in Charlotte, North Carolina, 2004-08-07
      - Sandra Clory interviewed in Charlotte, North Carolina, 2004-08-07
    - AFC 2005/015: MV131, 1 miniDV
      - Viola Williams interviewed by Hannah Rosenzweig in Greensboro, North Carolina, 2004-08-06 (2 of 2)
      - Event and performance in Charlotte, North Carolina, 2004-08-07
    - AFC 2005/015: MV132, 1 miniDV
      - Tammy R. Johnson interviewed by Hannah Rosenzweig in Charlotte, North Carolina, 2004-08-07
      - Bus ride from Charlotte, North Carolina to Columbia, South Carolina, 2004-08-07
    - AFC 2005/015: MV133, 1 miniDV
      - Event in Summerton, South Carolina, 2004-08-08
    - AFC 2005/015: MV134, 1 miniDV
      - Event and church service in Summerton, South Carolina, 2004-08-08
      - Nathaniel Briggs interviewed in Summerton, South Carolina, 2004-08-08
      - Hattie Stukes interviewed by Nery Ynclan in Summerton, South Carolina, 2004-08-08
    - AFC 2005/015: MV135, 1 miniDV
      - Event in Columbia, South Carolina, 2004-08-08
      - Unidentified woman interviewed in Columbia, South Carolina, 2004-08-08
    - AFC 2005/015: MV136, 1 miniDV
      - Group discussion of Elloree school integration in Orangeburg, South Carolina, 2004-08-09
      - Jim Sulton interviewed in Orangeburg, South Carolina, 2004-08-09 (1 of 2)
    - AFC 2005/015: MV137, 1 miniDV
      - Jim Sulton interviewed in Orangeburg, South Carolina, 2004-08-09 (2 of 2)
      - Mrs. Weber interviewed in Orangeburg, South Carolina, 2004-08-09
      - Diane Johnson interviewed in Orangeburg, South Carolina, 2004-08-09
      - Mary Elizabeth Ravanell interviewed in Orangeburg, South Carolina, 2004-08-09
    - AFC 2005/015: MV138, 1 miniDV
      - James Colbert interviewed by Andy Bowley in Tallahassee, Florida, 2004-08-12 (2 of 2)
    - AFC 2005/015: MV139, 1 miniDV
      - Billie Sue Hulsey interviewed by Andy Bowley in Birmingham, Alabama, 2004-08-14
      - Kenneth Mullinax interviewed by Andy Bowley in Birmingham, Alabama, 2004-08-14
      - Tour of Birmingham, Alabama, 2004-08-14
    - AFC 2005/015: MV140, 1 miniDV
      - Warren G. Brown, Sr., interviewed by Andy Bowley in Montgomery, Alabama, 2004-08-15
      - Velma May McNear interviewed by Andy Bowley in Montgomery, Alabama, 2004-08-15
      - Ernest B. Terrell interviewed by Andy Bowley in Montgomery, Alabama, 2004-08-15
    - AFC 2005/015: MV141, 1 miniDV
      - Valda Harris-Montgomery interviewed by Andy Bowley in Montgomery, Alabama, 2004-08-15
      - Scott B. Smith, Jr., interviewed by Andy Bowley in Montgomery, Alabama, 2004-08-15
      - Helen Carlile interviewed by Hannah Rosenzweig and Dan Lewis in Montgomery, Alabama, 2004-08-15
      - Silvia Chavez interviewed by Hannah Rosenzweig in Montgomery, Alabama, 2004-08-15